kimonolabs.com 2018-08-07

# None

Last Updated: 22 Dec 2013

kimono is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.

This Privacy Policy (the "Policy" or "Privacy Policy") covers kimono, Inc. ("kimono", "we", "us", or "our") and describes the types of information we gather from people visiting www.kimonolabs.com (the "Site") and from individual users interacting with the applications we provide to third parties and how we use such information. We understand the importance of privacy and accordingly, treat all information received in a responsible manner. By accessing the Site, you agree to be bound by this Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please do not use the Site or our services. Each time you use the Site or services, the current version of the Privacy Policy will apply. Accordingly, when you use the Site or services, you should check the date of this Policy (which appears at the top) and review any changes since the last version.

## 1\. Information we may collect from you

We may collect and process the following data about you:

  * Information that you provide us by completing forms on our sites. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our site or subscribing to our service including contact details such as name, email address and phone number.
  * Information that you provide us by completing surveys on our site or as carried out by our approved third parties
  * If you contact us for customer or technical support, we may keep a record of that correspondence or conversation.
  * Information that you provide us when carrying out transactions through our site including payment details such as credit card information and billing addresses.
  * Information we receive from third party search engines such as Google, Yahoo and Microsoft (Bing and MSN) relating to your search activity.
  * Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data and the resources that you access.

### Uses made of the information:

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To carry out our obligations arising from any agreements entered into between you and us.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## 2\. IP Addresses and Cookies

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. This is statistical data about our users' browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.

We may also use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the Site and with the services and to provide you with personalized offers. A cookie is a small data file placed on your computer's hard drive that contains information that allows us to track your activity on the Site. The cookie itself does not contain any personal information; however, if you provide us any personal information the cookie may act as an identifier to tie your personal information to your IP address or computer. You may choose to delete cookies from your computer's hard drive at anytime or to disable cookies on your computer. If you delete cookies that relate to the Site, we may not be able to identify you upon your return to the Site. Additionally, if you disable your computer's cookies, you may not be able to access certain features of the Site or services that require that cookies be enabled. The Site's cookies cannot be used to read data from your hard drive and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other websites. Additionally, our cookies cannot be used as a virus, Trojan horse, worm, or any other malicious tool that could impair your use of your computer. Our cookies are used to help us better understand how you and other users use the Site so we can continue to provide a better, more personalized user experience on the Site. We also share website usage information about our Site with those interested in running targeted promotional campaigns on the Site.

## 3\. Children and Privacy

Our Site is not directed to children and we will not request personally identifiable information from anyone who we know to be under the age of 18, unless we have obtained verifiable parental consent from a parent or legal guardian. If we become aware that a user under the age of 13 has registered with our Site, provided personal information, and kimono has not obtained prior verifiable consent from a parent or legal guardian, we will immediately remove the user's personal information from our files.

## 4\. Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

## 5\. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## 6\. Changes to our Privacy Policy

Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page. We do not guarantee that you will be notified of any such changes.
